#### Hello

## I'm Kirsten Vandepas

CLIFTON PARK, NY 12065 (518) 275-5692 KIRSTENMATAN@GMAIL.COM

Portfolio: https://kvandepas.myportfolio.com/

I'm a New York based Digital Designer who is unafraid of complicated requirements, whether building from the ground up or adhering to branding. I bring years of experience from a multitude of media to craft elegant user interfaces with an emphasis on the end-user experience.

# **Experience**

APRIL 2019 - PRESENT

#### Adirondack Sign Company, Saratoga Springs NY - Designer

- Create design layouts for signage (building, dimensional, carved, vehicle wraps, digital vinyl).
- Vectorize and recreate company logos.
- Edit clients' artwork to become print ready.
- Set up files for print, flatbed, and router.
- Work directly with clients via phone or email on project design.
- Work with supervisor to submit design proposals to different towns for permit/DRC approval.
- Assisting with production using Roland printers to print media onto vinyl and contour cut colored vinyl.
- Create estimates & invoices; take payments & deposits.
- Customer service greeting, answering phones and taking payments.

#### FEBRUARY 2016 - OCTOBER 2018

## **Level Up Studios, Albany NY** - Client Manager / Product Designer

- Advise clients on attainable goals and develop project plans.
- Manage full project life cycle for clients and ensure top quality deliverables.
- Work with artists to create merchandise for their products.
- Work with different print shops and bulk companies directly to make sure art is correctly formatted for ordering products.
- Travel to conventions to bring in new clients and sell current clients merchandise.

#### NOVEMBER 2015 - FEBRUARY 2016

#### **Gracenote**, **Queensbury NY** - *Digital Image Editor*

- Collect photos, logos and other digital assets from publicists and websites.
- Place collect logos with correct film/tv show.
- Create logos for shows/specials with no artwork.
- Work within a team to divide and conquer requests from the station.

JUNE 2013 - OCTOBER 2013

### Dark Square FX, Brooklyn NY - Junior Compositor

- Integrate generated images into live action footage.
- Create 2D graphic elements.
- Edit material to match film noise and colors accordingly.
- Roto around objects to be taken out of scenes.

#### Education

NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

CareerFoundry - Technical Degree in UI/UX Design

Learned from industry professionals about user interface and experience to create applications from researching, wireframing, and prototyping to final designs across different platforms (IOS, Android, Tablet, Web).

SEPTEMBER 2011 - SEPTEMBER 2012

**The DAVE School** - Associate in Animation & Visual Effects

Worked with industry professionals to learn animation, modeling, compositing and visual effects.

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JUNE 2010

F. Donald Myers Education Center - Technical Degree in Graphic Design

Learned the adobe suite to complete different lessons such as; web design, photography, logo design, print design.

#### Film & IMBD Credit

Christmas Dreams, Knightmares, Golden Winter, Rise of the Zombies, Layover, 40 Days and Nights.

# **Internship**

2010

Hound Dog Graphics, Saratoga Springs NY - Intern

Assisted with logo creation and web design.

# Programs/Skills

• Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Indesign, Illustrator, XD, etc.) • Microsoft Suite • Flexi Design • Roland Versaworks • Quickbooks • Production File Setup • Typography • Figma • Graphic Design • Layout Design • UI/UX Design • Prototyping • Brand Guidelines • Print Design • HTML/CSS • Responsive Web Design • Wireframing • Vector Illustration • Project Management •